{
    "id": "92deadd1609143fc816464516b168cde",
    "title": "Such and such a",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "40236e841a1c48778b184f0f3157a821",
            "title": "Such And Such A",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You talk …………….. nonsense.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It took ………………….. long time to finish the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had ………………… difficulty finding accommodation in Beijing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are ……………….. fool.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was ……………….. difficult test that I couldn’t answer most of the questions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are having ……………….. terrible weather at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I won’t agree with any ……………. plan.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I won’t agree with ………………. plan.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had ……………… terrible experience yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ………………… lovely girl.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}